National Coalition to Abolish the Death Penalty; Records apap298
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1988-2006, Undated; 1; 12.55 cubic ft.
  - Adults, 1988-2006, Undated; 1.1; 9 cubic ft.
    - Washington, Earl (VA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 74)
    - Washington, Terry (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 75)
    - Washinton, Vinson (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 76)
    - Watkins, Paul Sodoa (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 77)
    - Watkins, Ronald (VA), 1998 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 78)
    - Watson, Herbert (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 79)
    - Weaver, LaTwon (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 80)
    - Weaver, Ward Francis (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 81)
    - Webb, Daniel (CT), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 82)
    - Weeks, Lonnie (VA), 1999 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 83)
    - Weeks, Dwayne (DE), 2000; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 84)
    - Weeks, Varnall (AL), 2000; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 85)
    - Welch, David (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 86)
    - Welcome, Herbert (LA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 87)
    - Weldon, Dana R. (SC), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 88)
    - West, Robert (TX), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 89)
    - Westley, Anthony (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 90)
    - Wharton, Robert (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 91)
    - Wheat, John (TX), 2001 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 92)
    - White, Excell (TX), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 93)
    - White, Larry (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 94)
    - White, Michael (AZ), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 95)
    - White, Ronald L. (CO), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 96)
    - Whitmore, Jonas (AR) Executed May, 11, 1994, 2005; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 97)
    - Whitt, Charles E. (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 98)
    - Wiggins, Kevin (MD), 1994; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 99)
    - Wilcher, Bobby Glenn (MS), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 100)
    - Wiley, William (MS), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 101)
    - Wilkerson, Ponchai (TX), 2000 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 102)
    - Williams, Bob Russell (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 103)
    - Williams, Christopher (PA), 1999; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 104)
    - Williams, Craig (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 105)
    - Williams, David Earl (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 106)
    - Williams, Dobie (LA), 1998; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 107)
    - Williams, Dorothy (IL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 108)
    - Williams, Harold (GA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 109)
    - Williams, Keith (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 110)
    - Williams, Kenneth (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 111)
    - Williams, Marlow (VA), 1999 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 112)
    - Williams, Melvin "Troy" (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 113)
    - Williams, Robert E. (NE) Executed December 2, 1997, Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 114)
    - Williams, Ronald (AZ), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 115)
    - Williams, Stanley (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 116)
    - Williams, Terrance (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 117)
    - Williamson, Johnny (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 118)
    - Wilson, James (SC), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 119)
    - Wilson, Kenneth (VA), 1998 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 120)
    - Wilson, Zachary (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 121)
    - Winkler, Domila (VA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 122)
    - Wise, Jessie Lee (MO), 1999 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 123)
    - Wood, Billy Joe (TX), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 124)
    - Woodruff, David (OK) Executed January 31, 2002, Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 125)
    - Woratzeck, William (SC), 1997; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 126)
    - Workman, Phillip (TN), 2000 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 127)
    - Workman, Winder R. (OK), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 128)
    - Wrest, Theodore John (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 129)
    - Wright, Bronte (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 130)
    - Wright, Douglas (OR), 1996; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 131)
    - Wright, Freddie Lee (AL), 2000 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 132)
    - Wright, Jermaine (DE), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 133)
    - Wuornos, Aileen (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 134)
    - Yarris, Nicholas (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 135)
    - Young, Caroline (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 136)
    - Young, Kevin D. (SC), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 137)
    - Young, Moses (MO), 2000 (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 138)
    - Young, Robert (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 139)
    - Zambrano, Enrique (CA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 140)
    - Zeigler, Thomas (FL), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 141)
    - Zeitvogel, Richard (MO), 1996; Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 142)
    - Zook, Robert (PA), Undated (Box 9 (1-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Juveniles, 1994-2002, Undated; 1.2; 2.97 cubic ft.
    Death row inmates under the age of 18
    - Alvarado, Steven Brian (TX) - 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Arroyo, Randy (TX) - 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Arthur, Mark (TX) - 17 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Barnes, Michael S. (AL) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Barraza, Mauro M. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 1 of 2], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Barraza, Mauro M. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 2 of 2], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Beazley, Napoleon (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Bernal, Johnnie (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Blue, David (MS) - 17 yr, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Brennan, Keith (FL) - Juvenile, 16 yr, 1999; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Cannon, Joseph J. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 1 of 3], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Cannon, Joseph J. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 2 of 3], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Cannon, Joseph J. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 3 of 3], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Cannon, Joseph (TX) - 17 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Capetillo, Edward (TX) - 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Cooper, Paula (IN) - 15 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Conyers. Robert L. (SC) - Juvenile, 16 yr, 1997; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Cousin, Shareef (LA) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 1 of 5], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Cousin, Shareef (LA) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 2 of 5], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Cousin, Shareef (LA) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 3 of 5], 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Cousin, Shareef (LA) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 4 of 5], Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Cousin, Shareef (LA) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 5 of 5], 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Dewberry, John C. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Dinkins, Justin W. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Dixon, Anthony J. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Domingues, Michael (NV) - Juvenile, 16 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Eddings, Monty L. (OK) - 16 yr, 1999 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Farina, Jeffrey (FL) - Juvenile, 16 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Foster, Ronald Chris (MS) - 17 yr, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Gibson, Exzavious (GA) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Golphin, Kevin (NC) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Graham, Gary L. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 1 of 4], 1999; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Graham, Gary L. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 2 of 4], Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Graham, Gary L. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 3 of 4], Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Graham, Gary L. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 4 of 4], 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Graham, Gary (TX) - 17 yr, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Graham, Gary (TX) - 17 yr, 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Graham, Gary (TX) - 17 yr, 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Graham, Gary (TX) - 17 yr, 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Hain, Scott Allen (OK) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Haroey, Derrick (PA) - Juvenile, 16 yr, 1999 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - High, Jose Martinez (GA) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Holley, William (MS) - 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Hudgins, Joseph (SC) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Hughes, Herman Lee Jr. (SC) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 1 of 2, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Hughes, Herman Lee Jr. (SC) - Juvenile, 17 yr [Folder 2 of 2, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Hughes, Kevin (PA) - Juvenile, 16 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Jones, Anzel Keon (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - Kambule, Azikiwe (MS) - Juvenile 16 yr [Folder 1 of 2, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Kambule, Azikiwe (MS) - Juvenile 16 yr [Folder 2 of 2, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Kambule, Azi (MS) - Juvenile, 16 yr, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Kambule, Azikiwe (MS) - 16 yr, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Kambule, Azikiwe (MS) - 16 yr, 1997; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Kambule, Azikiwe (MS) - 16 yr, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Lee, Percy (PA) - 17 yr, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Martinez, Miguel (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - McGilberry, Stephen (MS) - 16 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - McGinnis, Glenn Charles (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Miles, Laquan (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Mooney, Jerry (OK) - 16 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Ortiz III, Oscar (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Osborne, Larry (KY) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1998 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Mitchell, Gerald (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Monterrubio, Jose (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Patterson, Toronto (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Perez, Efrain (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Powers, T. Benjamin (SC) - Juvenile, 16 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Rey, Johnny (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Roach, Steve (VA) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - Richardson, Antonio (MO) - 16 yr, Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Snipes, David Paul (FL) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Sellers, Sean Richard (OK) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 1 of 2], 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Sellers, Sean Richard (OK) - Juvenile, 16 yr [Folder 2 of 2], 1997; 1999; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Sellers, Sean (OK) - 16 yr, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Simmons, Christopher (MO) - 17 yr, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Simmons, Christopher (MO) - 17 yr, Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Soriano, Oswaldo R. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1994; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Stanford, Kevin N. (KY) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1999; 2002; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Thomas, Douglas Christopher (VA) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1999; Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Thompson, William W. (OK) - 15 yr, 1996; 1999; 2002 (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Tilley, Joe Vance (OK) - 16 yr [Folder 1 of 2], Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Tilley, Joe Vance (OK) - 16 yr [Folder 2 of 2], Undated (Box 3 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Villarreal, Raul (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Wilkins, Heath (MO) - Juvenile, 16 yr, 1999; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Williams, Alexander E. (GA) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1996; 2000; 2002 (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Williams, Nanon M. (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Williams, Nanon (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Williams, Nanon (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Williams, Nanon (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Wills, Robert James (TX) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Womble, Curtis Ray (NC) - Juvenile, 17 yr, Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Wright, Dwayne A. (VA) - Juvenile, 17 yr, 1998; Undated (Box 4 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Innocence, 1998-2000, Undated; 1.3; 0.58 cubic ft.
    Death row inmates who were released
    - Adams, Randall (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Banks, Jerry (GA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Beeman,Gary (OH), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Bigelow, Jerry (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Bloodsworth, Kirk (MD), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Brandley, Clarence (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Brown, Jesse (SC), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Brown, Joseph (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Burrows, Joseph (IL), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Butler, Sabrina (MS), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Cobb, Perry (IL), 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Charles, Earl (GA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Croy, Patrick (CA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Cruz, Robert (AZ), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Deeb, Muneer (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
    - Ferber, Beil (PA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 16)
    - "Ford Heights Four" (IL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 17)
    - Frank, Leo (GA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 18)
    - Gauger, Gary (IL), 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 19)
    - Golden, Andrew (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 20)
    - Green, Joseph (FL), 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 21)
    - Guerra, Ricardo (TX), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 22)
    - Harris, Johnny (AL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 23)
    - Hauptmann, Richard (NJ), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 24)
    - Hernandez, Alejandro (IL), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 25)
    - Herrera, Leonel (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 26)
    - Jacobs, Sonia (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 27)
    - Johnson, Edward (MS), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 28)
    - Johnson, Sammuel (MS), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 29)
    - Jones, Ronald (IL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 30)
    - Kyles, Curtis (LA), 1998; 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 31)
    - Landano, James (NJ), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 32)
    - Lawson, Carl (IL), 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 33)
    - Macias, Federico (TX), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 34)
    - Manning, Steven (IL), 2000 (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 35)
    - Marsh, Guy (MD), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 36)
    - Martinez, Daniel (NM), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 37)
    - McMillian, Walter (AL), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 38)
    - Miranda, Roberto (NV), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 39)
    - Monroe, Donald (LA), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 40)
    - Porter, Anthony (IL), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 41)
    - Pitts, Freddie/ Lee, Wilbert (FL), 1998; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 42)
    - Ramos, Juan (FL), 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 43)
    - Richardson, James (FL), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 44)
    - Schlup, Lloyd (MD), Undated (Box 1 (1-Case Files), Folder 45)
    - Scott, Brandley (FL), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 1)
    - Skelton, John (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 2)
    - Smith, Clarence (NM), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 3)
    - Smith, Jay (PA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 4)
    - Smith, Steven (IL), 2000; Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 5)
    - Sutton, Josiah (TX), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 6)
    - Tillis, Darby (IL), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 7)
    - Vasquez, Dave (VA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 8)
    - Wallace, Robert (GA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 9)
    - Walker, Nathaniel (NJ), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 10)
    - Whitmore, George (NY), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 11)
    - Wilhoit, Gregory (OK), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 12)
    - Williams, Dennis (IL), 2000 (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 13)
    - Williams, Wayne (GA), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 14)
    - Zimmerman, Isidore (NY), Undated (Box 2 (1-Case Files), Folder 15)
- Publications, 1982-2004, Undated; 2; 1 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by subject
  Contains publications of national magazines, LifeLines, the official newsletters of the NCADP as well as publications by affiliate organizations.
  - Death Penalty Press, with inmate publication, 1988 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Death Penalty Press, 1995 January-1998 October (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Death Penalty Press, 1999 January2000 April (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Death Penalty Press, 2001 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Death Penalty Press, 2001 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Death Penalty Press, Juveniles, Undated (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Fundraising, 2004 May-2004 December (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Lifelines 1-10, 1982 Spring-1984 March (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Lifelines 11-20, 1984 April-1985 March (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Lifelines 21-30, 1985 April-1986 October (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
  - Lifelines 31-40, 1986 November-1988 June (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Lifelines 41-50, 1988 July-1990 October (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Lifelines 51-60, 1991 January-1993 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
  - Lifelines 61-70, 1993 July-1997 September (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
  - Lifelines 71-80, 1997 November-1999 April (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
  - Lifelines 83-90, 2000 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Lifelines 91-93, 2003 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
  - National Execution Alert, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
  - National Execution Alert, 1999 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
  - National Execution Alert, 2000 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 2001 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
- Subject Files, 1972-2005, Undated; 3; 5 cubic ft.
  This series includes reference material on death penalty law in both the United States and abroad. Items in this series relate to some aspect of the death penalty and focus on education. Subjects include juvenile executions, the cost of the death penalty, and its impact on victim and inmate families. Material consists of news articles, correspondence, newspaper clippings, press releases, statements, and reports.
  - Advocacy, 1983 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Abolition Movement, 1986 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Affiliate Packet, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Alabama, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Alternatives, 1993 April (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - American Baptist Churches, 1983 October (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - ACLU, 1984 June (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - American Ethical Union, 1988 April-1993 September (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1981 January (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - American Jewish Congress, 1983 October (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - American Orthopsychiatry Association, 1984 May (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Amnesty International, 1994 January (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Arguments, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Arkansas, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Arizona, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Banner - 'National Coalition Against the Death Penalty, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Bibliography of Publications by Subject [1 of 2], ca. 2001 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Bibliography of Publications by Subject [2 of 2], ca. 2001 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Bush, George W., 1997 November (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - California, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Canada Reinstatement Effort, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Cartoons, 1988 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Catholic Worker House, 1988 December-1994 February (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Celebrities, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1981 October 1992 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Christian Church, 1989 November (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Church of the Brethren, 1984 January-1994 October (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Cure, 1986 February-1995 July (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Citizens for Law and Order, 1991 February (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Clemency, 1993 October-1999 June (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Clippings - Bizarre, Undated (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Clippings, 1987 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Clippings, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Clippings, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Clippings, 1993 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Clippings, 1994 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Clippings, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Colorado, 2005 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Celeste Commutations, 1991 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Commutations Post-Furman, 1999 May (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Connecticut, 1995 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Consensual Executions/Suicide, 1989 (Box 1 (3-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Cost, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Cost, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Cost By State, 1982 April-1998 December (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Cost Study By General Accounting Office, 1989 September (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Criminal Justice Issues, Undated (Box 2 (3-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Data CD - WDI 2003 (Cd-r 1)